♪ ♪
♪ I got my drivers license last week ♪
♪ Just like we always talked about ♪
♪ ‘Cause you were so excited for me ♪
♪ To finally drive up to your house ♪
♪ But today I drove through the suburbs ♪
♪ Crying 'cause you weren’t around ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And you’re probably
With that blonde girl ♪
♪ Who always made me doubt ♪
♪ She’s so much older than me ♪
♪ She’s everything I’m insecure about ♪
♪ Yeah, today
I drove through the suburbs ♪
♪ ‘Cause how could I
Ever love someone else ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I know we weren’t perfect
But I’ve never felt this way ♪
♪ For no one ♪
♪ And I just can’t imagine
How you could be so okay ♪
♪ Now that I’m gone ♪
♪ Guess you didn’t mean
What you wrote in that song about me ♪
♪ 'Cause you said forever
Now I drive alone past your street ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And all my friends are tired ♪
♪ Of hearing how much I miss you but ♪
♪ I kinda feel sorry for them ♪
♪ ‘Cause they’ll never know you
The way that I do ♪
♪ Yeah today I drove through the suburbs ♪
♪ And pictured I was driving home to you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I know we weren’t perfect
But I’ve never felt this way ♪
♪ For no one ♪
♪ Oh, and I just can’t imagine
How you could be so okay ♪
♪ Now that I’m gone ♪
♪ I guess you didn’t mean
What you wrote in that song about me ♪
♪ ‘Cause you said forever
Now I drive alone past your street ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Red lights ♪
♪ Stop signs ♪
♪ I still see your face ♪
♪ In the white cars ♪
♪ Front yards ♪
♪ Can’t drive past the places ♪
♪ We used to ♪
♪ Go to ♪
♪ ‘Cause I still fucking love you, babe ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Sidewalks ♪
♪ We crossed ♪
♪ I still hear your voice ♪
♪ In the traffic ♪
♪ We’re laughing ♪
♪ Over all the noise ♪
♪ God I’m so blue ♪
♪ Know we’re through ♪
♪ But I still fucking love you, babe ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know we weren’t perfect
But I’ve never felt this way ♪
♪ For no one ♪
♪ And I just can’t imagine
How you could be so okay ♪
♪ Now that I’m gone ♪
♪ Guess you didn’t mean
What you wrote in that song about me ♪
♪ 'Cause you said forever
Now I drive alone past your street ♪
♪ Yeah, you said forever